Gabriel Lombardi

Summary

Data science and big data analytics student, and graduate in engineering by the Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul, focusing on production and process engineering. With experience in project development, is focusing currently in optimization and automation of processes and functions through programming languages.

Experience

Commercial Analyst – March 2024 to the present **Ultragaz**, Florianópolis.

- Business Intelligence.
- Dashboard maintenance.
- · Creating and updating indicators.
- Exploring new market and potencial clients.

Data Analyst – May 2023 to February 2024 **Figueirense FC**, Florianópolis.

- Performance analysis.
- Data extraction and database maintenance.
- Participating in report elaboration and presentation.
- Overseeing athlete development.

Planning and control consultant – February 2020 to January 2023

MRV engineering, Porto Alegre and Florianópolis.

- Costs management and service planning to improve strategy and process mapping.
- Developing projects to ensure the process flow.
- Ensuring conformity in building plans.
- Cooperating in effective, safe and sustainable construction sites.
- Process mapping.

Safety engineering intern – February 2020 to March 2020 NR Medical and Engineering, Curitiba

Civil engineering intern – March 2017 to December 2017 **Alves, Fardin Engineering,** Porto Alegre

Engineering intern – January 2017 to March 2017 **Hotel Consulte**, Porto Alegre

Education

Data Science and big data analysis – currently studying **Universidade Estácio de Sá (UNESA)**.

Bachelor of Engineering: Civil Engineering - 2019 Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul (UFRGS), RS

Post-graduation: Safety engineering – incomplete

Federal University of Technology - PR

Additional activities

Software experience: Excel, Visual Basic, Power BI, Word, PowerPoint, Project, Revit, AutoCAD 2D
 & 3D, Sony Vegas, SAP ECC;

Developer Certifications: Python, Django, Power BI – Udemy – 2023.
 Angular Framework – DIO – 2023.
 Software development good practices – MOOC Unicamp – 2023;

Javascript – Trybe – 2023.
AWS – DIO – 2023.
AWS – DIO – 2023.

- Product management: <u>Cubos Academy</u> 2023
- Certifications: Six-sigma Yellow belt certification 2015, Open dojo program, development of human competencies, strategic and entrepreneurship skills - Universidade da Experiência Uexp – Curitiba - 2016;
- Volunteering activities: Construction working in emergency houses Teto Paraná 2016;
- Internacional experience: CISV camps from 2010 through 2013 and AFS exchange program in Italy
 2012;
- Scientific initiation: Institute of hydraulic research UFRGS 2015. Technological Innovation Fair FINOVA UFRGS 2015.
- Published Articles: ANALYSIS OF THE DISCHARGE COEFFICIENT BEHAVIOR IN SMALL CONDUIT
 SYSTEMS AN EXPERIMENTAL STUDY XXI Brazilian symposium of water resources. Energy and water efficiency in sanitation Academic journal: Revista da Extensão UFRGS PROREXT.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Problem solving
- Organization
- Planning and control
- Process mapping
- Cooperation

Languages

- Portuguese fluent
- English fluent
- Italian advanced
- Japanese beginner